(Sheldon:)I guess we're done here.
Here, drink-slash-eat this.
- What is it?
- It's hot chocolate with a stick of butter.
(Howard:)Okay, why?
(Sheldon:)In the frigid temperatures
in the Arctic...
...we need to consume 5000 calories
a day to maintain our body weight.
(Leonard:)You know I can't eat butter.
I'm lactose intolerant.
(Sheldon:)Way ahead of you. That's an
I Can't Believe It's Not Butter! stick.
But, Mommy, all the other guys
are going to the North Pole.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)I don't care
what the other guys are doing.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)If the other guys jumped
in the Bay of Bengal...
(Mrs Koothrappali:)...and tried to swim to Sri Lanka,
would you?
(Raj:)If you were standing behind me nagging,
I might.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Don't talk back to your mother.
This trip is much too dangerous.
(Raj:)No, it's not. Howard, tell them.
Dr. and Mrs. Koothrappali, namaste.
I understand you're concerned.
If it'll make you feel better,
my mother is fine with me going.